chrisnguyen@zenonzeni.ca

Summary

Currently a 4th year honors student in information technology at York University & Tutoring at Code Ninjas on hw to program and make software applications. My goal is to become an IT Full Stack developer that has worked on projects using Java an object-oriented programming language, PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS (Bootstrap), JavaScript (JSON, JQUERY, AJAX), SQL (MySQL, Oracle) for testing, implementing, and designed front-end web pages, websites, and applications. I have personal experience in system administration and designing/testing web systems.

WORK EXPERIENCE & RELATED EXPERIENCE

Coding Instructor & Curriculum Developer June 2021 – Present

| 1 Year | Code Ninjas, Vogel Richmond Hill, Ontario

- In-person and virtually develop video games and teach ninjas how to make games, videos, robots.
- Teach how to make JavaScript games, Roblox games and Unity (C#) games.

Academic Peer Support Assistant | May 2020 – April

2022 | 2 Years | York University, Vaughan, Ontario

- Facilitate study session for students by analyzing, design, develop and test java programs.
- Students who took part of my study sessions do a whole grade letter better in the course.

Ride Operator | March 2018 - November 2019

| 2 Years | Canada Wonderland, Vaughan,

Ontario

- Participated in teams of more than ten and communicate with other associates to operate rides.
- We would follow best practices to meet ride performance goals and safety audits.

Web Developer | Volunteer | Indigenous Friends | Oct 2021 – Present

• Designing, developing, and deploying an AI Virtual Chat Bot using IBM Watson Assistant.

Personal and Academic Projects

Portfolio Website Project

Developed a website portfolio at https://zenonzeni.ca.

Web Camping Spot Reservation System (Prototype)

Developed a web-based information system at http://132.145.111.100/.

EDUCATION

Honors Bachelor Information Technology | 2018–2022 | GPA: B+|

York University, Vaughan, Ontario

Skills, Knowledge & Tools

Programming Languages, Frameworks and Data Format Knowledge.

• HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQUERY, AJAX, JSON, PHP, XML, XSL, and Java.

Database Languages

• SQL (MYSQL, SQLPlus, Oracle)

System Administration/DevOps Skills

• Linux/Unix, MySQL, Oracle DB, IBM cloud tools, AWS, Oracle, Apache, Tomcat, Key Encryption, SSH, FTP, Github, and Git.

Tools/Knowledge

• Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook, Word, Zoom, (NetBeans, Eclipse Visual Studios, IntelliJ), etc.